[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "What will I call you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "I", "call", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "Your royal highness.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "royal", "highness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "By what right?", "question_tokens": ["By", "what", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "By divine right if you must.", "answer_tokens": ["By", "divine", "right", "if", "you", "must", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Why should I waste my time listening?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "I", "waste", "my", "time", "listening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Because I have a right.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "have", "a", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Do you think it is?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "That will have to be for others to decide or for me to decide when I'm so old that I'm other -- it'll be in knotting away trying to grasp at any memories I have dictating my memoirs.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "will", "have", "to", "be", "for", "others", "to", "decide", "or", "for", "me", "to", "decide", "when", "I", "'m", "so", "old", "that", "I", "'m", "other", "--", "it", "'ll", "be", "in", "knotting", "away", "trying", "to", "grasp", "at", "any", "memories", "I", "have", "dictating", "my", "memoirs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What did you think of Bertie, of King George VI?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "Bertie", ",", "of", "King", "George", "VI", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "I found the most -- I fell in love with him completely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "found", "the", "most", "--", "I", "fell", "in", "love", "with", "him", "completely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bertie", "George VI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "I've actually heard some of the real footage of King George VI, and it's painful listening, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "actually", "heard", "some", "of", "the", "real", "footage", "of", "King", "George", "VI", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "painful", "listening", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George VI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "When you're in the supermarket, and you're trying to order something, do you lapse into Bertie, just start stammering because you just got so used to that voice?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "in", "the", "supermarket", ",", "and", "you", "'re", "trying", "to", "order", "something", ",", "do", "you", "lapse", "into", "Bertie", ",", "just", "start", "stammering", "because", "you", "just", "got", "so", "used", "to", "that", "voice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "When I'm in a supermarket, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "'m", "in", "a", "supermarket", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bertie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Aren't we both lucky?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "we", "both", "lucky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, I thought I was lucky.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "I", "was", "lucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Do you quite like the fact of having been Darcy and having been in \"Bridget Jones'\" stuff where you play the classic archetype of charmer that the last two great roles you've had, \"Single Man\" and \"King's Speech,\" you're not actually playing that kind of character?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "quite", "like", "the", "fact", "of", "having", "been", "Darcy", "and", "having", "been", "in", "``", "Bridget", "Jones", "'", "''", "stuff", "where", "you", "play", "the", "classic", "archetype", "of", "charmer", "that", "the", "last", "two", "great", "roles", "you", "'ve", "had", ",", "``", "Single", "Man", "''", "and", "``", "King", "'s", "Speech", ",", "''", "you", "'re", "not", "actually", "playing", "that", "kind", "of", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "''", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I do relish that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "relish", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Darcy", "Bridget Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "You prefer it as an actor?", "question_tokens": ["You", "prefer", "it", "as", "an", "actor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "But where does that leave you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "where", "does", "that", "leave", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Leave me taking out the trash.", "answer_tokens": ["Leave", "me", "taking", "out", "the", "trash", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Is she amused by your sex symbol image?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "amused", "by", "your", "sex", "symbol", "image", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "She's Italian, of course?", "question_tokens": ["She", "'s", "Italian", ",", "of", "course", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "She's Italian.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "Italian", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 171, "question": "How's your Italian?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "your", "Italian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "(Speaking in foreign language)", "answer_tokens": ["(", "Speaking", "in", "foreign", "language", ")"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Do you think all -- you know, do you find John Major sexy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "all", "--", "you", "know", ",", "do", "you", "find", "John", "Major", "sexy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Not personally, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "personally", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Major"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "When we come back, what's the biggest turkey?", "question_tokens": ["When", "we", "come", "back", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "biggest", "turkey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "We don't go there.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "go", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Any kind of normality in that relationship?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "kind", "of", "normality", "in", "that", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "IRTH: You know, I -- we've made it 15 years together.", "answer_tokens": ["IRTH", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "we", "'ve", "made", "it", "15", "years", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "How do you avoid the shallow pitfalls of temptation like a thrown Hollywood heartthrob away?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "avoid", "the", "shallow", "pitfalls", "of", "temptation", "like", "a", "thrown", "Hollywood", "heartthrob", "away", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "It does help to actually realize that however stunning the person who's, you know, fluttering eyelashes at you is she doesn't do anything to match up to your wife.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "help", "to", "actually", "realize", "that", "however", "stunning", "the", "person", "who", "'s", ",", "you", "know", ",", "fluttering", "eyelashes", "at", "you", "is", "she", "does", "n't", "do", "anything", "to", "match", "up", "to", "your", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "And you don't really talk about them much, but as they get older, your children, would it unnerve you if they wanted to go into acting?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "do", "n't", "really", "talk", "about", "them", "much", ",", "but", "as", "they", "get", "older", ",", "your", "children", ",", "would", "it", "unnerve", "you", "if", "they", "wanted", "to", "go", "into", "acting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "What would he have made of your success?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "your", "success", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "Well, he's still around.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "still", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Have I?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Apparently.", "answer_tokens": ["Apparently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What's the biggest turkey?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "biggest", "turkey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "We don't go there.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "go", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What's the worst?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "worst", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "We can't, you see.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "ca", "n't", ",", "you", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":"], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Because --", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "It's amazing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "amazing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Spectacular.", "answer_tokens": ["Spectacular", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Can I have all of them?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "have", "all", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "You can have two.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "have", "two", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Do you like to do love scenes?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "to", "do", "love", "scenes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I like the idea of them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "the", "idea", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Do you think no one would notice if you stepped in as a body double?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "no", "one", "would", "notice", "if", "you", "stepped", "in", "as", "a", "body", "double", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "ORGAN: This is what I'm thinking.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "This", "is", "what", "I", "'m", "thinking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "I mean can any wife enjoy watching their beloved husband romping with Scarlet Johansson?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "can", "any", "wife", "enjoy", "watching", "their", "beloved", "husband", "romping", "with", "Scarlet", "Johansson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I doubt it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "doubt", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scarlet Johansson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "But if you were to introduce him yourself, how would you describe him?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "were", "to", "introduce", "him", "yourself", ",", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I would describe him as my geisha girl.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "describe", "him", "as", "my", "geisha", "girl", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Humpty Dumpty"]}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Where is your hair?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "your", "hair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Oh, I'm doing a film about Humpty Dumpty down here.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'m", "doing", "a", "film", "about", "Humpty", "Dumpty", "down", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 418, "question": "How would you describe your relationship with Colin?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "your", "relationship", "with", "Colin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, we --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Do you believe in the royal family?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "in", "the", "royal", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Have you met any of them?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "any", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "I have briefly met Prince Charles and I think he's a very, very interesting, very civil and civilized person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "briefly", "met", "Prince", "Charles", "and", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "a", "very", ",", "very", "interesting", ",", "very", "civil", "and", "civilized", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Do you think the institution is a good one?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "institution", "is", "a", "good", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I like really voting.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "really", "voting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Unelected institution isn't really your cup of tea?", "question_tokens": ["Unelected", "institution", "is", "n't", "really", "your", "cup", "of", "tea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "It is a problem for me, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "problem", "for", "me", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia"]}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Have you had a private bet between each other as to who may actually walk away with the old statue?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "a", "private", "bet", "between", "each", "other", "as", "to", "who", "may", "actually", "walk", "away", "with", "the", "old", "statue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I'll let that one drift over to Australia.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "let", "that", "one", "drift", "over", "to", "Australia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Helena Bonham Carter", "Colin"]}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "CC", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Geoffrey?", "question_tokens": ["Geoffrey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I think Helena Bonham Carter will get it, and Colin and I won't, and will be furious.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Helena", "Bonham", "Carter", "will", "get", "it", ",", "and", "Colin", "and", "I", "wo", "n't", ",", "and", "will", "be", "furious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Is it as nerve wrecking as I imagine it would be?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "as", "nerve", "wrecking", "as", "I", "imagine", "it", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "It's a post modernist experience I think, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "post", "modernist", "experience", "I", "think", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "What are you so afraid of?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "so", "afraid", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Your poisonous words.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "poisonous", "words", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What was Colin like to work for, in terms of him working to you as a producer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "Colin", "like", "to", "work", "for", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "him", "working", "to", "you", "as", "a", "producer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "That -- that credit, I think, is more on the creative side.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "--", "that", "credit", ",", "I", "think", ",", "is", "more", "on", "the", "creative", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I'm very well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Did you ever meet the queen mother?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "meet", "the", "queen", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Yeah, I did, actually, when I was very, very young, a long, long time ago, at the premier of \"A Room With a View.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "did", ",", "actually", ",", "when", "I", "was", "very", ",", "very", "young", ",", "a", "long", ",", "long", "time", "ago", ",", "at", "the", "premier", "of", "``", "A", "Room", "With", "a", "View", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "The two heavily-ego'd movie stars?", "question_tokens": ["The", "two", "heavily-ego", "'d", "movie", "stars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "They talk a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "talk", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Duke of York"]}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Duke of York?", "question_tokens": ["Duke", "of", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Yes, the Duke of York.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "the", "Duke", "of", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Am I considered the enemy?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "considered", "the", "enemy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "You will be if you remain unobliging.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "will", "be", "if", "you", "remain", "unobliging", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Have you, Geoffrey?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", ",", "Geoffrey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "But then ask him.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "then", "ask", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Geoffrey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "What are your early thoughts, Helena?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "early", "thoughts", ",", "Helena", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Helena"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "But what are your views on Colin Firth the sex symbol?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "are", "your", "views", "on", "Colin", "Firth", "the", "sex", "symbol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "I did fancy him in his uniform, with the medals.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "fancy", "him", "in", "his", "uniform", ",", "with", "the", "medals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Firth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Do you remember that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "You like him as Darcy?", "question_tokens": ["You", "like", "him", "as", "Darcy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Yeah, yeah, I did, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "yeah", ",", "I", "did", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Would you fancy Piers in the same uniform?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "fancy", "Piers", "in", "the", "same", "uniform", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elaine Page"]}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "Wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "To see a woman come out who is a 48-year-old spinster in a tiny Scottish village, and everyone's laughing at here, and she's able to sing like Elaine Page, and we're all sniggering and everything else.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "see", "a", "woman", "come", "out", "who", "is", "a", "48-year-old", "spinster", "in", "a", "tiny", "Scottish", "village", ",", "and", "everyone", "'s", "laughing", "at", "here", ",", "and", "she", "'s", "able", "to", "sing", "like", "Elaine", "Page", ",", "and", "we", "'re", "all", "sniggering", "and", "everything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "If Susan Boyle was here now Colin, singing \"I Dreamed a Dream,\" would you dream involve the Academy Awards end of February, standing there clutching the gong, making the speech you've been preparing and practicing for probably 40 years?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Susan", "Boyle", "was", "here", "now", "Colin", ",", "singing", "``", "I", "Dreamed", "a", "Dream", ",", "''", "would", "you", "dream", "involve", "the", "Academy", "Awards", "end", "of", "February", ",", "standing", "there", "clutching", "the", "gong", ",", "making", "the", "speech", "you", "'ve", "been", "preparing", "and", "practicing", "for", "probably", "40", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "``", "PRP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "EX", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "You know, the thing that happens with this age -- this extraordinary advanced age I've reached is that it's not the long-term memory going.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "thing", "that", "happens", "with", "this", "age", "--", "this", "extraordinary", "advanced", "age", "I", "'ve", "reached", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "not", "the", "long-term", "memory", "going", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["February"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Academy Awards"], "PERSON": ["Susan Boyle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "CD", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "Is it the pinnacle?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "pinnacle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "I don't know how much one even really dares to contemplates dreams on that scale, really.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "much", "one", "even", "really", "dares", "to", "contemplates", "dreams", "on", "that", "scale", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "Can I chip in here?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "chip", "in", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "IRTH: Yeah, go on, darling.", "answer_tokens": ["IRTH", ":", "Yeah", ",", "go", "on", ",", "darling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "How could we forget?", "question_tokens": ["How", "could", "we", "forget", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "He couldn't have been king without her.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "could", "n't", "have", "been", "king", "without", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]